Forgive Us Our Trespasses is a drama, war film directed by Ashley Eakin.
Targeted by Nazis as they hunt down and murder people with disabilities, a boy with a
limb difference makes a daring decision while running for his life.
Peter, played by Knox Gibson.
Eva, played by Hanneke Talbot.
German officer, played by Justin Mader.
Karl, played by Nathaniel McParland.
Older boy, played by Tyler Hutchings.
Young Woman, played by Noah Lamanna.
Forgive Us Our Trespassing is a piece by graffiti artist Banksy
depicting a kneeling boy with a spray-painted halo.
The image can be found on a wall in Salt Lake City, Utah.
In 2010, the image was distributed in the form of posters to
promote the artist's film Exit Through the Gift Shop.
In March 2010, an official large-format version of the artwork was displayed at
London Bridge Station in a collaboration between Banksy and Don't Panic.
Transport for London gave permission for this artwork to be hung only if the original image was
altered to remove the yellow dripping spray paint halo, so as to not encourage graffiti.
The print exhibited but removed within 48 hours after the halo was
repaired by "either Banksy or one of his people”.
Only one large-format poster of Forgive Us Our
Trespassing now remains in existence.
The film explores themes of neo-nazism, ss (nazi
schutzstaffel), nazi officer, german occupation, disability.
The tone is emotional.